دعم المشرف شاهد على
kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
There are some here too.
Come and get it, quick!
Come over here!
There are more on this side.
They're all mine.
All of these are mine.
Give it back to me.
Mine.
I'll kill you.
They're all mine.
Go to hell!
Don't fight with me.
Jiu Ye, go to hell!
Jiu Ye.
Have you forgotten Jiu'er?
How can you be so cruel?
Jiu'er, why is it you?
لماذا انت هنا؟
Why are you like this, Jiu'er?
Jiu Ye.
Why do you want to kill me?
Don't you love Jiu'er anymore?
You betrayed me.
You.
If I could kill you once,
I can kill you a second time.
Enxi.
Where's the stuff?
Where is it? Where is it?
The stuff.
Enxi.
My stuff is gone.
Where's the compass?
Did you take it? Did you take it?
I can't find the stuff.
I've looked everywhere, can't find it.
You took it.
You took it, Jiu Ye. I didn't.
I didn't steal it. I can't find it.
You took it. Give it back.
I didn't take it.
Jiu Ye.
Jiu... you.
Give me the compass.
It's our turn to get rich.
I don't have the compass.
Don't come closer.
Jiu Ye.
I told you before,
someone wants to steal your stuff.
Cui En.
Jiu Ye, you're awake.
Jiu Ye.
I found some mushrooms in the woods.
I made some soup.
Drink it while it's hot.
Enxi.
Thank you for your hard work.
مُطْلَقاً.
Thanks to Jiu Ye for saving me yesterday.
Of course I had to save you.
You're always loyal to me.
I didn't just save you.
I'll take you to enjoy wealth and glory.
Thank you, Jiu Ye.
Then I'll get back to work.
Jiu Ye.
ينظر.
Azure Dragon Ridge.
هذا صحيح.
That's it.
دعنا نذهب.
You should eat something.
You haven't eaten since yesterday.
Your body can't take it.
Hai... Haiyue.
This trip probably won't end well for us.
لا لا.
That's not what I meant.
I mean,
on this trip,
we don't know what will happen next.
Did I say something wrong again?
I know what you mean.
No, you don't.
I have a lot I want to tell you.
I'm afraid if I don't say it now,
I won't get another chance.
Haiyue.
I... I've been an orphan since I was little.
I've never seen my parents since birth.
But I was lucky.
Sometimes villagers gave me food.
Sometimes I dug through trash
to find something to eat.
I survived, somehow.
Later, traffickers sold me as a blood slave.
I thought that was my fate.
I'd die in there sooner or later.
But luckily, I met Brother Jin.
And met Chief Luo.
And then I met you.
I felt I wouldn't die anymore.
I even found a family.
Haiyue.
I'm not as good as you.
You know how to hunt ginseng.
You can heal people.
You're even a chieftainess.
If Brother Jin hadn't helped me,
I'd be nothing now.
Haiyue.
أنا...
I just want to keep looking at you.
Seeing you smile makes me so happy.
I just want to stay by your side.
Watching you.
Yan Baobao.
You have to keep your word.
From now on, you must always look at me.
Stay by my side.
Don't leave me, not even a step.
هنا.
Brother Jinzi.
Where should we go next?
Azure Dragon Ridge.
Jiu Ye, look.
The shelter Jin Shisan built last time.
I see it.
اذهب أبعد قليلاً وسوف تصل إلى
Azure Dragon Ridge.
لقد قمت بفحص التضاريس هنا
في وقت مبكر من هذا الصباح.
وتمتد المنطقة لأكثر من
عشرة كيلومترات.
كلها منحدرات وجدران شديدة الانحدار.
ولكن هناك شيء غير عادي
في هذا المكان.
باوباو.
هل تتذكرون تكريم
الغابة؟
إنه عندما يكون كل نبات وشجرة
ينمو في نفس الاتجاه.
هذا صحيح.
إنه مثل هذا لعدة أميال
في كل مكان.
أكثر إثارة للدهشة مما حدث عندما
استخرجنا بخور شينلونج.
إنه أمر أكثر إثارة للدهشة.
يقولون أن ملك الجينسنغ
على وشك الظهور.
ويأتي مرة كل ستين دورة.
يبدو أن ملك الجينسنغ
سيظهر قريبًا.
دعنا نذهب، دعنا نذهب، دعنا نذهب!
يذهب!
يا للأسف.
جيو يي.
أسقط مسدسك.
تينغشوان، ابن أخي.
ماذا تفعل؟
أيها الوغد العجوز.
من الصعب قتلك.
حتى السم لن يستطيع القضاء عليك.
ما هو السم؟
فطر العالم السفلي.
لإرسالك إلى
طريق الجحيم.
من العار أن هذا وعاء الحساء.
لكن قتل تلك الساحرة إينشي
كان يستحق ذلك.
لقد كان الأمر يستحق ذلك.
ابن الأخ.
أنظر هنا.
أنا وأبوك كنا أخوة بالقسم.
لقد شاهدتك تكبر.
ماذا تريد؟
أخبر عمك.
ماذا أريد؟
تسألني ماذا أريد؟
أريدك أن تعيد
لي جيو إير.
هل تستطيع فعل ذلك؟
لقد قتلتها.
لقد قتلتها بنفسك.
ابن الأخ.
كل هذا من أجل المرأة؟
هل تعرفها حقا؟
هل تفهمها؟
إنها لا تعرف
ما هو الحب.
إنها تهتم فقط
باسم عائلتك.
لو كنت فقيرا،
انها لن تنظر اليك حتى.
هراء!
إسمع يا رجل عجوز؟؟؟
أنا الوحيد
في قلبها.
انا فقط.
اتفقنا؟؟؟
بمجرد أن وجدنا الجينسنغ،
هربنا معًا.
يانغ لاوبا.
لقد قمت بتربية أحمق مريض بالحب.
هل تعلم لماذا
هل ذهب المنصب
إلى أختك؟
لأنك عديم الفائدة،
مجرد عديم الفائدة.
أنت؟؟؟
أنا الوريث الحقيقي
لعائلة يانغ. قلها!
أنت عديم الفائدة. قلها!
من انا؟
أنا وريث عائلة يانغ.
أنت وريث عائلة يانغ.
أنت وريث عائلة يانغ. أنا؟؟؟
انا؟؟؟اذهب إلى الجحيم!
إنكسي.
إنكسي. إنكسي.
إنكسي، ما الأمر؟
سأجد طريقة
لإنقاذك، أختي.
أخت.
لا تهتم.
هل أنت ذكي جدًا؟؟؟
أنت تعلم أنه لا يوجد طريقة لإنقاذي.
هيا، انهض.
استيقظ.
أخت.
أنا آسف.
لقد كنت مخطئا.
يانغ تينغكسوان.
يانغ تينغكسوان، استيقظ!
لقد شربت كثيرا مرة أخرى.
يانغ تينغكسوان، استيقظ.
استيقظ.
استيقظ!
أخ.
أخي استيقظ!
مات أمي وأبي في سن صغيرة.
لقد كنا وحدنا
منذ أن كنا أطفالاً.
لقد عانينا كثيرا
من الآخرين.
لن اسمح لهم
بالدوس علينا بعد الآن.
لقد ولدنا جميعا بشرًا.
لماذا يجب أن نكون
أقل من أي شخص آخر؟
أرفض قبول هذا المصير.
سأقرر مصيري بنفسي.
أريد أن أرتفع فوقهم
جميعًا.
أريد؟؟؟أنا...
مم.
إنكسي.
أنت أختي الطيبة.
لكن اللطف
لا يجلب لك سوى التنمر.
نحن الإبنتين
من عائلة كوي؟؟؟
لا يمكن أن يكون ضعيفًا
ولطيفًا في نفس الوقت.
أريد لمتجر Cui Ginseng
أن يزدهر أيضًا.
أخت.
أستطيع أن أرى أن هذا الأحمق
يعاملك بشكل جيد.
أنا حقا أحسدك.
أخت.
لا أستطيع البقاء معك
بعد الآن.
اعتنِ بنفسك.
لم أعتني
بك جيدًا يا أختي.
أختي؟؟؟أختي.
هنا.
أعتقد أنني أرى أبي.
إنكسي. إنكسي. إنكسي.
إنكسي. إنكسي.
أن جيو يي؟؟؟
إنه حقا لا يرحم.
خذهم بعيدا.
نعم نعم.